Alan W. Steelman papers, Inclusive: 1960-2003, Bulk: 1973-1976
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Correspondence, 1972-1976, undated; 4
  - 1972-1973, undated; 1
    - Topical, 1972-1973; 4
      - Employment Recommendations and Information, 1973, undated (Box 23, Folder 6)
      - General Felt, Dallas, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 7)
      - Inaugural, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 8)
      - Haiti Translinear, 1970-1976 (Box 23, Folder 9)
      - Harvard Institute on Politics, 1972-1973 (Box 23, Folder 10)
      - Howard Lela, Pleasant Grove CC, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 11)
      - Rabbi Lieb Pinter, 1973 August 10 (Box 23, Folder 12)
      - Pleasant Grove, Lake June Road, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 13)
      - Redistricting Plan, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 14)
      - Redistricting (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 15)
      - Redistricting (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 23, Folder 16)
      - Redistricting (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - 1974, 2
    - Alpha, 1974; 1
      - Aa-Al, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 2)
      - Am-Az, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      - Ba, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      - Bb-Bl, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 5)
      - Bm-Bri, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      - Brj-Bz, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 2)
      - Ca-Cg, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      - Ch-Cl, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 4)
      - Co, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      - Cp-Cz, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      - Da-De, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
      - Df-Dz, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      - E, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      - Fa-Fl, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      - Fm-Fz, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 6)
      - Ga-Gn, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Go-Gz, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      - Ra-Ri, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      - Rj-Rz, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      - Sa-Se, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      - Sf-Sl, 1947 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Sm-So, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Sp-Sz, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Td-Th, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Ti-Tz, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - U, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - V, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Wa-Wi, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Wf-Wi, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Wj-Wz, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - XYZ, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Incoming, 1974; 2
      - General (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - General (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Thanks, Praise, & Congratulations (1 of 4), 1974 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Thanks, Praise, & Congratulations (2 of 4), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Thanks, Praise, & Congratulations (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Thanks, Praise, & Congratulations (4 of 4), 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Outgoing, 1974; 3
      - General, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - General (1 of 2), 1974 January-May (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - General (2 of 2), 1974 January-May (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - General (1 of 2), 1974 May-June (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - General (2 of 2), 1974 May-June (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Thanks, Praise, & Congratulations (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Thanks, Praise, & Congratulations (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Topical, 1974-1975; 4
      - Character Recommendations, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Bishop College, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Employment Recommendations & Information, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - National Security Classification (1 of 8), 1974 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - National Security Classification (2 of 8), 1974 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - National Security Classification (3 of 8), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - National Security Classification (4 of 8), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - National Security Classification (5 of 8), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - National Security Classification (6 of 8), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - National Security Classification (7 of 8), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - National Security Classification (8 of 8), 1974 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Social Security, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Texas Bicentennial, 1974 (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Garland (1 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Garland (2 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Garland (3 of 3), 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Garland League of Cities, HUD Urban Observatory Program, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Ditchley Foundation, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Federal Procurement Conference, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Procurement Conference Brochure, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Fort Sill Apaches, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - LBJ Library, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - Oglesby Group, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - Postal Delta Center, 1974-1975 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - 1975, 3
    - Alpha, 1975; 1
      - Aa-Al, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Am-Az, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - Ba, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Bb-Bl, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Ba-Bri, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - Bri-Bz, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - Ca-Cg, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - Ch-Cl, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Cl-Coo, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Cop-Cz, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Da-De, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Df-Dz, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - E, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Fa-Fl, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Fm-Fz, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Ga-Gn, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Go-Gz, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Ha (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Ha (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Hb-Hl, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Hm-Hz, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - I, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Ja-Ji, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Jj-Jz, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Ka-Kh, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Kj-Kz, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - La-Li, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Lj-Lz, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Ma, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Mb-Mi, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Mc, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Mj-Mz, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - N, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - O, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Incoming, 1975; 2
      - General (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - General (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - General (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Greetings and Thanks (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Greetings and Thanks (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing, 1975; 3
      - Greetings (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Greetings (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Thanks (1 of 4), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Thanks (2 of 4), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Thanks (3 of 4), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Thanks (4 of 4), 1975 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Topical, 1975-1976; 4
      - Angels, Inc. & Children Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Architectural Engineering Contacts, GSA, DIOD, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Automobile Industry, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Balch Springs Post Office, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Baylor, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Bicentennial Activities, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - Children’s Haven, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Education, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Education Recommendations, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Employment Assistance (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Employment Assistance (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Garland Foods, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Garland, Duck Creek, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - General Clippings, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - International Trade Commission Slide Fasteners Association, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 15)
      - MESBIC Financial Corp. of Dallas, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - Mesquite, City of, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Mexican American Council for Economic Progress, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - National Federation of Independent Businessmen (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - National Federation of Independent Businessmen (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Older Americans, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Postal Delta Center, Postal Service, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - 1976, 4
    - Incoming, 1976; 1
      - General, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Greetings and Thanks, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Outgoing, 1976; 2
      - General, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Greetings, Thanks, & Congratulations, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Thanks, 1976 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Topical, 1973-1976; 3
      - Coastal Bend Migrant Council, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Duck Creek Project, 1973-1976 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Garland City Council, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - MESBIC Financial Corporation of Dallas, 1976, undated (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Departments and Agencies, 1973-1976; 5
  This series includes Steelman's contact with various federal agencies and governmental departments arising from constituent concerns and recommendations for posts in the departments. It is alphabetically ordered according to folder title and/or department name. Prominent departments in this series are the U.S. Postal Service; Housing and Urban Development; Health, Education, and Welfare (HEW), and The White House. The series also contains a lone folder on housing in the State of Texas in 1975 and is in good condition.
  - ACTION, 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Agency for International Development, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - American Revolution Bicentennial Commission, 1973-1975 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - CIA and the Cult of Intelligence, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board, 1974-1976 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1974 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Comptroller General of the United States, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Cost of Living Council and Price Controls, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Department of Commerce, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Department of Defense, Corps of Engineers, 1973-1976 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Department of Defense, Middle East & Mediterranean Trip, 1975 November-December (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Department of Defense, General, 1973-1974 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Department of Defense, General, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Department of the Interior, 1973-1975 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Department of Justice, 1974-1976 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Department of Justice, Law Enforcement Education Program (LEEP) Funds (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Department of Justice, LEEP Funds (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Department of Justice, Recommendations, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Department of Labor, 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Department of Labor, Recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Department of Labor, S.S. United States, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Department of State, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Department of State, Recommendations, 1973-1975 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Department of Transportation, 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Department of Transportation, Recommendations, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Department of Treasury, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (EPA), General, 1973-1976 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - EPA, State Underground Injection Control Program, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Commission, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1973-1974 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Federal Communications Commission, Communication Media, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Federal Agency Administration, 1973-1976 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Federal Energy Office, 1974 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Federal Energy Office, Whitco Inc. Case, 1975 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Federal Power Commission, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Federal Trade Commission (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Federal Trade Commission (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - General, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - General Accounting Office, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - General Services Administration, 1974-1975 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Government Printing Office, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Hearings, CIA, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Health, Education, & Welfare (HEW), General, 1973-1974 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - HEW, General, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - HEW, General (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - HEW, General (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - HEW, Task Force on Indochina Refugees (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - HEW, Task Force on Indochina Refugees (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - HEW, Nursing Home Regulations, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - HEW, Pharmaceutical Regulations (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - HEW, Pharmaceutical Regulations (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Housing, State of Texas, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Housing & Urban Development, General, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Housing & Urban Development, General (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Housing & Urban Development, General (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Housing & Urban Development, General (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Housing & Urban Development, General (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Housing & Urban Development, General (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Housing & Urban Development, Real Estate Settlement Procedures Act, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - International Trade Commission, Duty Rates, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Library of Congress, Librarian Qualifications, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1973-1976 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - National Endowments for the Humanities, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - National Science Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1974 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Office of Minority Business Enterprise (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Office of Minority Business Enterprise (2 of 2), 1974-1976 (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - President’s Council on Physical Fitness and Sports, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Small Business Administration, 1973-1975 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - The White House, General, 1974-1975 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - The White House, General, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - The White House, Recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - The White House, Recommendations, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - The White House, Recommendations, 1976 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - The White House, “The Administration”, 1974 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - The White House, The White House Fellows Program, 1973-1976 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General (1 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 50, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General (2 of 2), 1975-1976 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Postal Service, General, 1976 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - U.S. Postal Service, Balch Springs Post Office, 1974 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Postal Service, Postage Rate Increases, 1973 (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - U.S. Postal Service, Postage Rate Increase, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - U.S. Postal Service, Lakewood Post Office, 1973-1974 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Postal Service, Removal of Xerox Machines, 1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - U.S. Postal Service, Valencia and Cordova Mailbox, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Veterans Administration, 1974-1976 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- District, 1972-1976, undated; 6
  This series encompasses Steelman's work in the Fifth Congressional District of Texas with two subseries: Dallas and Texas. The Dallas subseries contains materials on AMTRAK's service to that city, community activism, and records of Steelman's trips in January and February 1973. Particular localities, numerous industries (mining, air travel, tool manufacturing, food processing), and state and local relations figure prominently in the Texas subseries. This series remains in good condition.
  - Dallas, 1973-1975; 1
    - Adams, Bryan, 1972 January (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Amtrak, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - City, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - City, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - Community Action, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Community College, 1973 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Community Council, 1974-1975 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - County, 1975 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - County Community Action, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - Dallas County Community Action Committee (DCCAC): Para Legal Program, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Government Accounting Office Cosmetology, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Legal Services Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Police, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Southwest Metroplex, 1975 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - Transatlantic Routes for Dallas-Fort Worth Airport, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - Trips, 1973 January 1 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Trips, 1973 February 8-19 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Urban Park Baptist Singers, 1973 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Texas, 1973-1976, undated; 2
    - Airlines-Mutual Aid Pact, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Citrus Industry, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - City of Sachse, Flood Hazard Boundary Map, 1975-1976 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - City of Seagoville, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - Hayes—Morales Case, 1976 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - Matagorda Island, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - Office of State — Federal Relations, 1975 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - Recommendations, 1973-1974 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - Reed, Dick, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Richardson Airport (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Richardson Airport (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - Rodriguez, Umberto, 1973-1975 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Seagoville, 1973 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of State, 1974-1975 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Skyjacking — Dr. Hubbard, undated (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - State & Local Affairs (1 of 3), 1975 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - State & Local Affairs (2 of 3), 1975 (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - State & Local Affairs (3 of 3), 1975 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - State & Local Affairs (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - State & Local Affairs (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - State & Local Affairs (3 of 3), 1976 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - State Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - State Affairs (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - State Affairs (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - State Affairs (1 of 2), 1974 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - State Affairs (2 of 2), 1974 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - State Constitution, 1974 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - State Legislature (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - State Legislature (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - State of Texas, 1975 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Stein, Brent, 1974-1975 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Stokes, Jim, 1973-1974 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Supreme Beef Processors, 1975-1976 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Texas Institute for Medical Assessment, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Texas Institute for Medical Assessment, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Texas Nursing Homes Assoc., 1974-1975 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Thorsen Tool Co., 1972-1974 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Unimark Agencies — Charles Terrell, 1974 (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Urban Affairs, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Varo, Inc., 1973 (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Ventures, 1973-1974 (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - Vestal Coal, 1974-1975 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Wade, Jim, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Wadley Blood Bank, 1972-1974 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Williamsburg Community Corp., Kent Village, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- Legislation by Committee, 1973-1976, undated; 7
  This series contains eleven subseries: Agriculture, Animal Welfare, Appropriations, Armed Services, Banking and Currency, Foreign Affairs, Government Operations, Interior and Insular Affairs, Judiciary Committee, Ways and Means, and Cabinet Committee on Spanish-Speaking People. A District of Columbia sub-subseries as well as ones on the National Budget, Education and Labor, Health, House Administration, and Labor reside in the Banking and Currency subseries. Interior and Insular Affairs contains a sub-subseries on Immigration and Naturalization and the Judiciary Committee subseries has three sub-subseries: Post Office and Civil Service, Science and Astronautics, and Small Business. The series is in alpha order with the exception of the Education and Labor sub-subseries, which is in chronological-topical ordering. This series is in good condition.
  - Agriculture, 1973-1976; 1
    - General (1 of 7), 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - General (2 of 7), 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - General (3 of 7), 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - General (4 of 7), 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - General (5 of 7), 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - General (6 of 7), 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - General (7 of 7), 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - General (1 of 3), 1976 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - General (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 3), 1976 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Animal Welfare, 1974; 2
    - General, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Appropriations, 1974; 3
    - Nixon Transition Money, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Housing, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - General, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Defense Department, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Armed Services, 1973-1976; 4
    - General, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Amnesty, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Commissaries, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Military, 1974 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - General, 1973 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Military (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Military (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Military Surveillance Bill, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Military, Mayaquez, Puerto Rico, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Military, F-18 (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Military, F-18 (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Military, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Military, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Military, 1975-1976 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Banking Committee, Undated (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Builders ROBO, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Countdown, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - General (1 of 3), 1974 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - General (2 of 3), 1974 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - General (3 of 3), 1974 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - General (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - General (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - General (1 of 2), 1976 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - General (2 of 2), 1976 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Housing, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Jones-Blair Lead-Based Paint, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Banking and Currency, 1973-1976; 5
    - District of Columbia, 1973-1974, 1976; 1
      - General, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 6)
      - General, 1974 (Box 64, Folder 7)
      - General, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - National Budget, 1973-1974; 2
      - General (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 64, Folder 9)
      - General (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 65, Folder 1)
      - General, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Education and Labor, 1973-1976; 3
      - Busing 48 and 124, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 3)
      - Busing (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 65, Folder 4)
      - Busing (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 65, Folder 5)
      - Dallas Skill Center, 1973 (Box 65, Folder 6)
      - Education (1 of 3), 1973 (Box 65, Folder 7)
      - Education (2 of 3), 1973 (Box 66, Folder 1)
      - Education (3 of 3), 1973 (Box 66, Folder 2)
      - Financial Aid (1 of 2), 1973 (Box 66, Folder 3)
      - Financial Aid (2 of 2), 1973 (Box 66, Folder 4)
      - Health Diabetes, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 5)
      - Health Insurance, 1973 (Box 66, Folder 6)
      - Health (1 of 6), 1973 (Box 66, Folder 7)
      - Health (2 of 6), 1973 (Box 67, Folder 1)
      - Health (3 of 6), 1973 (Box 67, Folder 2)
      - Health (4 of 6), 1973 (Box 67, Folder 3)
      - Health (5 of 6), 1973 (Box 67, Folder 4)